ASHLEY HASSARD

Raleigh, NC 27616 | (919) 888-1569 ashleynhassard@gmail.com

WEB DESIGNER

Versatile and driven web designer. Novice but strong ability to maintain and provide ongoing design of a website, create promos and ad banners, and incorporate content that is critically important. A team player who is also self-directed. Combines form and function to create engaging and effective websites, mobile applications, and more. Plans site design and functionality through site navigation by categorizing content and funneling traffic through that content. Extensive education and experience in multiple disciplines to include; information technology, naval military training, technical aviation and maintenance solutions, fire and emergency medical services training. Excellent analytical and problem-solving skills with effective interpersonal communication.

Hard Skills:

- HTML/CSS3/PHP
- Angular/Typescript
- JavaScript
- Python

- Web Analytics
- Social Media Marketing
- SEO/SEM
- WordPress

- Mobile site design
- Adobe Photoshop/Premier
- Adobe Illustrator/After Effects

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Webmaster | Carolina Roller Derby, Inc. Raleigh, NC | 2018 - present

Manages the web presence of Carolina Roller Derby a 501(c)(3) organization run solely by skaters and volunteers. Coordinates and works closely with the board of directors to ensure ongoing consistency and innovation in web content and design, accurate and secure content, and easy site navigation for a memorable end-user experience. Responsibilities include; Debugging issues that arise with the performance of the websites, maintain plug-ins and pixels for tracking. Plan for future changes to websites including content and graphics. Perform periodic technical and SEO audits. Participate in the development of website goals to meet organization needs. Lead website design, development and maintenance, while ensuring brand standards and SEO best practices. Lead ongoing efforts to the re-brand of the organization starting Jan '19.

Avionics Technician | Boeing, Seymour Johnson AFB | 2018 – present & U.S. Navy (Petty Officer 2nd Class) | 2011-present Performed aerospace vehicle system testing and modification to support military and contracted civilian flight operations and maintenance production; troubleshooting complex electrical systems to isolate mechanical/electrical faults; modification of systems through repair, replacement or upgrade of faulty components to correct failures and implement changes. Performed organizational level maintenance and repair on aviation electronics systems; conducted troubleshooting, fault isolation, system modification and testing for aircraft communications/radar/navigation systems, electrical sensors, electronic data link servers, command and control tactical displays and associated support equipment. Trained junior sailors in the operation, testing and repair of aircraft and support equipment components.

Firefighter/Paramedic | Dayton, Ohio area and multiple southeast U.S. regional fire rescue | 2006 – 2017 Rendered emergency and non-emergency services to critically ill or injured persons; executed medical care and life-saving measures when facilitating mobile transfers between accepting facilities, made prompt decisions regarding safety and medical decisions based on environmental situation, standing orders, protocols and medical direction. Performed complex diagnostic and medical procedures while working in extreme environmental conditions and conducting technical rescue operations. Interacted with community through educational activities designed to bring awareness to fire prevention and ways to save lives.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

AAS in Information Technology and **Multiple Certifications**| Wake Technical Community College | 2019 **Avionics Organizational Maintenance Technician Certification** |Center for Naval Aviation Technical Training | 2012 **Ohio Paramedic Certification** | Butler Tech | 2009

Firefighter Emergency Medical Technician Certification | Sinclair Community College | 2006